你不会相信我刚才无意中
You will not believe the conversation
听到盖比和他的朋友杰克说了什么
I just overheard between Gabe and his friend Jake.
这么说来你是窃听人家谈话
So you were snooping.
我才没有窃听
I wasn't snooping.
我只是踮起脚尖下楼梯
I was tiptoeing down the stairs.
那时我只不过停下来想休息一下
When I paused for a break.
哈  继续吧  窃听狂
Aha, go on, snoopy.
好了  总之
Okay, so anyway,
盖比说“希瑟真性感”
Gabe says, "Heather is so hot."
然后杰克也附和了句“真性感”
And Jake's all, "so hot!"
然后盖比又说“我真的很喜欢她
And then Gabe says, "I really like her,
但我一见到她就紧张得连嘴都张不开”
But I'm too nervous to talk to her."
杰克又说“老兄  别害羞  鼓起勇气
And Jake's all, "dude, you gotta hike up your skirt.
约她出来”
And ask her out."
鲍伯  咱们如何处理这件事
Bob, what are we gonna do about this?
不如给你挂个铃铛  好让孩子知道你驾到了
How about we make you wear a bell so the kids can hear you coming?
我说的是盖比面对心仪的女生羞于开口这件事
I'm talking about Gabe being too shy to talk to girls.
再一次  狂暴老娘又要出马解决问题了
Once again, mama ames has to solve the problem.
噢  窃听狂外加干预狂
Ooh, snooping and meddling.
狂暴老娘今天激情燃烧了
Mama ames is on fire today.
你们知道吗  我觉着车库里还有个铃铛
You know what? I think I got a bell in the garage.
你忙什么呢  小鬼
What you got there, kiddo?
我只是看看以前的老照片
I'm just going through my old school photos.
这几天我们还会去拍照的
We're getting our pictures taken in a couple of days.
所以我下定决心  这次坚决不能像个傻子一样
And I am determined for once to not look like a dork.
以前的照片怎么傻了
What's wrong with your pictures?
好吧  让我们追忆一下往昔
Well, let's stroll down memory lane, shall we?
这是幼儿园照的
Here I am in kindergarten.
悲剧啊  那天正好赶上学习静电这块儿
Yeah, that was the day we learned about static electricity.
我刚用脑袋蹭过气球
I just finished rubbing my head with a balloon.
好了  宝贝  不可能所有照片都这么惨吧
Well, honey, they can't all be that bad.
噢  你太小瞧我了  这张  三年级时候的
Oh, can't they? Here I am again, third grade.
那天早上  咱的婴儿盖比朝我扔了个吸管杯
That was the morning that baby Gabe threw a sippy cup at me.
婴儿盖比  完全就是一个小拉登
Baby Gabe... such a little terror.
-我们当时还认为长大了就变好了呢  -是啊
-And we thought it was just a phase. -Yeah.
嘿  老妈  我如何才能拍出一张好看点儿的照片
Hey, mom, how can I make sure that I take a good picture?
照着我的方法做
Do what I do when I wanna look good.
去买件新衣服
Go buy a new outfit.
是吗  那你  那你能支付新衣服的价格吗
Well, would you... would you pay for this new outfit?
噢  别天真了  我只管出点子  不出钱
Oh, sweetheart, I give advice, not money.
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
■
翻译： Johnny-Z
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
■
校订： line
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z  liloelva
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第二季第十七集
Good Luck Charlie  S02E17  P.J in the City
这节目真搞笑  叫什么名字
This show is so funny. What's it called?
“咯咯笑”  查莉的最爱了  对吧
"The Gurgles." The favorite show, right, Charlie?
好吧  是我的最爱
Well, it's my favorite show.
噢  我该走了
Oh, I'd better go,
但走之前  我想和你照张相
But first, I wanna picture of you and me.
明天可以吗
Can it wait till tomorrow?
我想先修剪下胡子
It'll give me a chance to trim my beard.
胡子  没看见你有胡子啊
Beard? I don't see anything.
是吗  我都让它滋生一个月了
Really? I've been growing it out for, like, a month.
但是  我真的需要照张相
Well, I really need a picture now.
好吧  但是家里没人
All right. Well, nobody else is home,
所以就让查莉帮忙照相吧
So Charlie will have to take it.
好了  查莉  耽误你一会儿
Okay, Charlie, come here for a second.
这很简单  一学就会  听着
This is very easy. Very easy, okay.
你向下按这个按钮  等到一半时进行对焦
You're gonna push this little button halfway down to focus.
然后等这绿灯从闪烁到一直亮时
Then when the green light goes from flashing to solid,
然后把这个按钮按到底  直到你听到咔嚓一声
Push it all the way down until you hear the click.
明白了吗
Okay?
好了吗
还是如咱们自己来吧
Or we can just take it ourselves.
预备  笑一笑
Ready? Smile.
看一看
Let's see.
噢  很不错啊
Oh, it's beautiful.
好了  我走了
Well, uh, I'd better go.
-给你  -谢谢
-There you go. -Thanks.
再见  PJ
Goodbye, P.J.
噢  哇  嘿
Oh, whoa, hey.
呃  你还好吧
Uh, are you okay?
我很好  就是
I'm fine. It's just that...
我很好
I'm fine.
好吧  明天见
Okay. See you tomorrow?
再见
Bye.
有点儿怪
That was weird.
噢  天啊  这破胡子让我抓狂了  我要去刮胡子
Oh, man, this thing is driving me crazy. I gotta go shave.
斯宾塞
Spencer?
泰迪  嗨
Teddy, hi.
嘿  这双人字拖太适合你了
Hey, you're rockin' those flips.
你在这里干什么
What are you doing here?
还赤膊上阵
Without a shirt?
噢  我  我在这里工作
Oh, I, uh... I work here.
-噢  -稍等  好了  扔吧
-Oh. -Hang on. Yeah, I'm open.
投的漂亮  老兄
Nice toss, brah.
这就是工作吗
So this is work?
是啊  我是店内的模特
Yeah, I'm an in-store model.
负责卖一些有青春活力的夏日用品
It's all part of selling the hot teen summer lifestyle.
嘿  这太阳镜真不赖
Hey, those shades are tight.
那你就光  站在这里
So you just... you stand here.
然后装傻充愣吗
And you act dumb?
这是我听过的最愚蠢的工作
That's the stupidest job I've ever heard of.
其实  我可以用超低的价格来买这里的衣服
Well, I get a huge discount on all the clothes.
噢  我也想要这份愚蠢的工作
Oh, I want a stupid job too.
-我猜我可以帮你安排一次面试  -好的
-I guess I could get you an interview. -Okay.
嘿  冲浪裤挑的不错啊
Hey, righteous boardshorts, dude.
而且价格也不贵  可以省钱买点儿切达奶酪了
And they won't set you back too much cheddar.
没错  而且看着不赖
Yeah, that's right. Lookin' gouda.
高德奶酪
Gouda?
（注：音似good）
我  我还以为要进行奶酪呼应呢
I... I thought we were doing a cheese thing.
亲爱的  PJ
<i>Dear P.J.,</i>
我有话要对你说  所以我留了张纸条给你
<i>I have something to tell you,</i> <i>so I'm writing this note.</i>
但是鉴于你不善于阅读
<i>But since you're not</i> <i>a big reader,</i>
所以我就把话给录下来了
<i>I taped it</i> <i>for you instead.</i>
长凳上有个录音机  请点击播放
<i>There's a boom box</i> <i>on the bench. </i> <i>Hit "play."</i>
这件事有点儿棘手
<i>So this is kind of hard.</i>
我要告诉你的是
<i>I have to tell you</i> <i>that...</i>
抱歉  我说不下去了  还是去看纸条吧
<i>I'm sorry.</i> <i>I can't go on. </i> <i>Just go back to the note.</i>
我这里有些坏消息
<i>I've got some really</i> <i>bad news.</i>
我爸被调动到纽约工作了
<i>My dad has been transferred</i> <i>to New York City,</i>
也就意味着  我也会去纽约
<i>Which means</i> <i>I'm moving there.</i>
我本想亲自告诉你的  但是说再见时的痛苦
<i>I wanted to tell you,</i> <i>but it made me so sad</i> <i>to say goodbye,</i>
让我无法承受
<i>I just couldn't.</i>
我会一直想你的
<i>I'll miss you forever.</i>
噢  忘了说了  我是斯凯勒
<i>Oh, by the way,</i> <i>this is Skyler.</i>
现在请继续听收音机
<i>Now press "play" again.</i>
什么情况
What's going on?
给  自己读吧
Here, read that.
PJ  替你惋惜
P.J., I'm so sorry.
老爸  她是  她是我的挚爱
Dad, she was... she was the love of my life.
我是说  我永生都将告别欢乐了
I mean, I'll never be happy again.
好了  我了解现在的感受
Okay, I know it feels that way now...
完了  我彻底崩溃了
No, I'll never be happy again.
-PJ  话说早了  -没有  就是永远
-P.J., in time... -No, never!
好吧  好吧  你告别了欢乐时代
All right, all right, you're never gonna be happy again.
你怎么能这么说我
How can you say that?
-噢  你干嘛呢  -吃零食
-Oh, what you doing? -Having a snack.
我能为您效劳什么呢
Can I help you with something?
没事  只是想和我儿子聊聊天
Nope, just making convo with my boy.
或者应该称之为  小伙子
Or should I say young man?
好了  我闪了
Yeah, I'm out of here.
不可以  给我坐椅子上
Nope. Sit in that chair.
-来谈一谈学校生活  -好吧
-Let's talk about school. -Okay.
-你的同学如何啊  -同学
-How are your classmates? -My classmates?
男同学啊  女同学啊
Boy classmates, girl classmates...
希瑟啊
Heather.
希瑟  等等  你怎么知道她的
Heather? Wait, how'd you know about her?
你老爸是个窃听狂
Your dad is such a snoop.
总之  如果你想找我谈谈她  我随时恭候
Anyway, if you ever wanna talk about her, I'm here for you.
算了  咱俩从来不谈论这种话题
No, we are never having that conversation.
盖比  我可是女的  我知道女生喜欢什么
Gabe, I'm a girl. I know what girls like.
宝贝  我只想给你提供正确的信息
Honey, I just want you to have the right information.
老妈  如果我想了解关于女生的信息
Mom, if I need information about girls,
我会从众所周知的渠道获得
I'll get it where all 12-year-olds get it:
去问十三岁的
From a 13-year-old.
可爱至极
How cute.
还以为我会就此罢手呢
He thinks this is over.
好了  记住  尝试下
Okay, just remember, try and be...
-装傻  对吧  明白了  -没错
-Not smart. Right, got it. -Yeah, okay.
泰迪  这位是经理  雨儿
Teddy, this is my manager Rain.
噢  雨儿  我喜欢
Oh, rain. I love it.
感觉  湿湿的
It's like so... Wet.
这么说你俩一起去学校
So you two go to school together?
没错  我俩是学校的铁哥们
Yeah, that's right. We're school buds.
我是说  当我不想上学的时候
I mean, when I bother to show up.
那你的学习如何
And how are your grades?
不怎么好  差不多七十多分
Not good... mostly cs.
六十多分  是六十多分
And ds ds, mostly ds.
我喜欢这女孩儿
I like this girl.
那你业余时间都喜欢干什么啊
So what do you like to do in your free time?
我喜欢拥抱自己
I like to hug myself?
我喜欢放松  放松一下
I like to chill. Chill! I like to chill.
很好
Cool.
好了  现在来看看如何应对沙滩球
Okay, let's see how you do with a beach ball.
好的  你只需要  好的
Yeah, you're just gonna wanna... okay.
干什么呢
What was that?
如果你在这里工作
If you're gonna work here,
你就要让我认为你很享受接这个沙滩球
You have to make me believe that you love catching beach balls.
-好的  明白了  -很好  再来一遍
-Okay okay, all right. -Yeah. Again.
好有意思
It's fun.
我觉着你是干这份工作的材料
I think you could be hot teen summer material...
太好了  爽歪歪了
Awesome, stoked.
但是你需要先在你这白皙的皮肤上下点儿功夫
...If you do something about that pale skin.
对不起  什么
Sorry, what?
你要看起来像是天天晒在太阳底下一样
You have to look like you live in the sun.
在这里工作
At H.T.S...
-太阳就是上帝  -没错
-The sun is your daddy. -Mm-hmm.
那你明天四点再来
So come back tomorrow at 4:00.
如果你变成褐色皮肤  这份工作就归你了
If you have a tan, you've got a job.
-好的  -好的
-Okay. -Okay.
我该怎么办  我在太阳底下很容易晒伤的
What am I supposed to do? I burn too easily in the sun.
像我们一样  弄点儿古铜色化妆品
Do what we all do... get some bronzer.
往身上喷颜色  轻松搞定
A spray-on tan. I can do that.
-谢了  -小意思
-Thanks. -Yep.
好了  我该走了
Well, I should probably get going.
你也知道明天有物理考试
You know we have that big physics test tomorrow.
你能小点儿声吗  难道你想被炒鱿鱼吗
Would you keep your voice down? Do you wanna get us all fired?
-噢  抱歉  -嘘
-Oh sorry. -Shh!
嘿  看我在门口发现了什么
Hey, look what I found on the porch.
“亲爱的邓肯家”
"dear Duncan family,"
我给你们留了这张字条  但我决定你们还是听收音机吧
I wrote you this note, then decided you should hear it from me instead.
“请按播放”
"Press 'play.'"
嘿  大家好
<i>Hey, guys,</i>
我决定跟随斯凯勒一同前往纽约  这样我们就不用分开了
<i>So I decided to follow Skyler</i> <i>to New York so we can</i> <i>be together.</i>
斯凯勒的父母同意我可以先和他们在一起
<i>Skyler's parents said</i> <i>I could stay with them</i>
直到我可以自己谋生
<i>Until I land</i> <i>on my feet.</i>
最后  感谢你们给了我这个和睦的家
<i>So... Thanks for</i> <i>being a great family</i>
不用为我担心
<i>and don't worry about me.</i>
保重
<i>Love you.</i>
噢  忘了说了  我是PJ
<i>Oh, by the way,</i> <i>this is P.J.</i>
哼
Hmm...
看来某人没有选好儿子谈谈女生的事啊
Looks like somebody talked to the wrong son about girls.
嘿  查莉  我是爸爸啊
Hey, Charlie, it's daddy.
我正在纽约给你打电话呢
I'm calling you from New York City.
能让妈妈接电话吗
Can you put mommy on the phone?
Put mommy on the phone.
能  能让妈妈接电话吗
C-can you put... put mommy on the phone?
或者挂断电话
Or just hang up.
匹萨来了
Pizza's here!
斯凯勒  是我  PJ的爸爸
Skyler, it's me. It's P.J.'s dad.
噢  这下尴尬了  我们只订了份中号匹萨
Oh, this is awkward. We only ordered a medium.
其实  我只是在找PJ
Actually, I'm just looking for P.J.
噢  PJ啊
Oh, P.J.
你能相信他为了我如此费尽周折吗
Can you believe he came all this way for me?
-真是太浪漫了  -啊
-It's so romantic. -Ah.
那你上来的时候看见匹萨外卖员了吗
So did you see a pizza delivery guy on your way up?
他在哪呢
So where is he?
我不知道  我刚才不是问你了吗
I don't know. I just asked <i>you</i> <i>where he is.</i>
我说的是PJ  乖乖  PJ在哪
P.J., honey. Where's P.J.?
-噢  他在工作  -他已经找到工作了
-Oh! He's at work. -He got a job already?
是啊  他想赚钱来买自己的公寓
Yeah, he wants to make money to get his own apartment.
他在华尔街工作
He's working on wall street.
你是说华尔街吗
He's working on wall street?
其实  是华尔街底下
Well, under wall street.
他们说纽约人没人情味儿
they say new yorkers can be kind of rude
那为什么不赏点儿钱给这个丹佛男
why not give money to this Denver dude?
一点儿小钱也无妨
a few coins or dollars sure wouldn't spoil it
为什么我要在一个臭气熏天的地方把歌唱
why am I singing in what smells like a toilet? .
好了  搞定了
Okay. All right.
“保持颜色在皮肤上一小时
"keep bronzer on for one hour.
然后冲洗掉  就可以享受您的古铜肤色了”
Then rinse and enjoy your golden tan."
听起来挺简单的
Sounds simple enough.
好了  那我就
Okay, so...
定一个小时
One hour.
现在只要等着闹钟响了
Now I just have to wait for the ding.
现在几点了
What time is it?
三点
3:00.
提醒你下  你变成橘色了
By the way, you're orange.
谢谢提醒  我知道我变成橘色了
Yeah, I know I'm orange.
为什么闹钟没响
Why didn't the timer go off?
查莉  你都做了什么
Charlie, what did you do?
淡定  以后你就会对此事哈哈大笑的
Relax, someday you'll laugh about this.
我今天就笑一笑
I'm gonna laugh about it today.
噢天啊  难以置信  我希瑟
Oh my gosh, I can't believe I, Heather grouper,
居然在盖比·邓肯的府中
Am in Gabe Duncan's house.
我还以为他不知道有我这个人呢
I didn't think he even knew I existed.
那个  显然是有我这个人的
Well, obviously I exist.
不然我不会身处盖比·邓肯的府中
Or I wouldn't be here in Gabe Duncan's house,
而且面积比我想象的还要大些
Which is so much bigger than I thought.
有件事很有意思  有些房子
Isn't it so funny how some houses.
从外面看很小  但是里面却很大
Look so small from the outside, but are big on the inside?
但其他那些房子  从外面看很大
And other houses look big on the outside,
其实里面则不然
But are small on the inside?
好了  我说完了  您问的什么问题
Well, anyway, what was the question again?
你好啊
How are you?
很好  非常的好
Good. Great actually,
因为我正在盖比·邓肯的家中
Because I'm in Gabe Duncan's house!
好了  了解了  了解了
Yeah, we got that. We got that.
盖比
Gabe!
你怎么在这里
What are you doing here?
你妈妈邀请我来的  她说你喜欢我
Your mom invited me. She said you like me.
老妈  来厨房和你说句话
Mom, a word in the kitchen?
好的
Okay.
马上回来
Be right back.
为什么你要告诉烦人的希瑟我喜欢她
Why did you tell annoying Heather I like her?
因为我知道我儿子有点儿害羞
Because I know my little boy is too shy...
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你为什么叫她“烦人的希瑟”
Why did you call her "annoying Heather"?
我不喜欢这个希瑟  我喜欢的是性感希瑟
I don't like <i>her.</i> <i>I like hot Heather.</i>
有两个希瑟
There's two heathers?
其实班里有五个希瑟
In my class there are five heathers.
其他那四个希瑟我都可以将就
And I would have been okay with any of the others...
聪明希瑟  高个儿希瑟
Smart Heather, tall Heather,
甚至是多毛希瑟
Even hairy Heather.
儿子  我现在开始
Boy, I'm really starting.
后悔你把我卷入这场希瑟之战中了
To wish you hadn't gotten me involved in this.
我又累又饿  请大家施舍点儿吧
I'm tired and hungry, so don't be so selfish
什么都可以
anything helps
除了贝类食物  我过敏
but I'm allergic to shellfish. .
嘿  老爸  你怎么来了
Hey! Dad, what are you doing here?
来找你谈谈
We need to talk.
嘿  嘿  嘿  嘿
Hey hey hey hey!
嘿  快闪开  麦尼
Hey, get lost, mimey.
这是我的地盘
This is my territory.
快点儿  滚回你的破地方去
Go on, hit the imaginary road.
-快滚开  -喔  喔  喔  PJ
-Get outta here. -Whoa whoa whoa, P.J.!
-你这是怎么了  -在纽约呆上一天半
-What happened to you? -Been in New York a day and a half.
它会让你改变自己的
The city changes you, man.
好了  你需要回家了
Okay, you need to come home.
不成  斯凯勒和我要呆在一起
No no, Skyler and I belong together.
我了解你的感受
I know how you feel,
但是看看那只蟑螂有多大
But look at the size of that cockroach.
斯凯勒是我一生的挚爱
Skyler is the best thing that's ever happened to me.
我们注定要在一起
We're meant to be together.
PJ  你才十七岁
P.J., you're 17 years old.
你会怎么知道那些
How can you possibly know that?
那好  我所知道的就是我不想离开她
Well, all I know is I don't wanna be apart from her.
你们不会永远都不能在一起
You might not be apart forever.
-什么意思  -当爱情来临时  有句俗话说的好
-What do you mean? -When it comes to love, there's a very old saying...
亲娘啊  好大的老鼠
Sweet mama, that's a giant rat!
这句话我的确听说过  但是
Yeah, I've heard that before, but...
不是  不是  俗话不是这么说的
No no no, that's... that's not the saying.
俗话就是
The saying is...
儿子  如果你爱她  就放开她
Son, if you love something, set it free.
如果她又回来了  那她就是你的了
If it comes back to you, then it's yours.
但如果她没回来  那她就和你无缘了
But if it doesn't, then it never was.
你怎么搞的
What happened to you?
可能颜色喷的有点儿过度
I may have overbronzed just a smidge.
我本以为你不会干出这么愚蠢的事情
I didn't think you'd pull off the whole dumb thing,
但结果出乎我的意料  你是自然呆
But it turns out you're a natural.
-泰迪  -噢  嗨  老板
-Teddy? -Oh hi, boss.
嘿  给我扔个沙滩球  老兄
Hey, why don't you toss me that beach ball, dude?
呜  耶
Whoo! Yeah!
你怎么是这个颜色
Why are you orange?
看  这是健康肤色
See, it's just a healthy glow.
嘿  老兄  给我把那个足球扔过来
Hey, brother, why don't you throw me that football?
噢
Oh!
-噢  -没事吧
-Ow. -Are you okay?
没事  没事
Yeah, I'm good. I'm fine.
嘿  浴巾不错啊
Hey, righteous beach towel, dude.
能借我用一下  擦擦血吗
Could I use it to wipe up some blood?
老妈  我们怎么办
Mom, what are we gonna do?
我们总不能藏在厨房里一辈子吧
We can't hide in the kitchen forever.
为什么不可以  我们有吃的  我们有喝的
Why not? We've got food. We've got drink.
老妈  你出去摆平她
Mom, you gotta get rid of her.
有点儿困难  我从未和女生分过手
This is really hard. I've never broken up with a girl before.
-好吧  我自己出马  -盖比  不要
-Fine, I'll do it myself. -Gabe, no.
希瑟  我和你说点儿事
Heather, I gotta tell you something.
什么事  盖比
Yes, Gabe?
老妈  你想说点儿什么吗
Mom, something you wanna say?
好吧  希瑟  事情是这样的
Okay. Heather, the thing is.
呃  现在的恋爱关系有点儿复杂
Um, there was a little mix-up about the who likes who thing.
噢  不会吧  盖比不喜欢我
Oh no! Gabe doesn't like me?
那是因为
Only because...
杰克喜欢你
Jake likes you.
哪个杰克
Which Jake?
有多少个杰克
How many are there?
四个  矮子杰克  皮包骨头杰克  高个杰克
Four. There's short Jake, skinny Jake, tall Jake...
我说的是一个红头发的胖墩儿
This one's stocky with red hair.
型男杰克吗
Hot Jake?
杰克们的水平都不怎么高
Standards for the Jakes are really low.
难以置信杰克居然喜欢我  他可是全能型人才
I can't believe Jake likes me. He's the total package...
红发  雀斑  笑起来像个香蕉
The red hair, the freckles, the way he always smells like bananas,
你是不知道  香蕉可是这个世界上唯一
Which in case you didn't know, are the only fruits in the world...
再见了  再见了
Bye-bye now. Bye-bye.
所以即使你找不到像我一样
So even though you won't find another guy.
迷恋你的男生
Who's as crazy about you as I am...
我会给你自由的
I set you free.
还有即使
And even though.
你找不到比我还迷恋你的女生
You'll never find a girl who's crazier than I am... About you...
你也是自由的
You're free too.
那事情就这样了
So I guess this is it?
看  这就是为什么我不想和你告别
See, this is exactly why I didn't want to say goodbye to you.
嘿  那我们就不告别
Hey, let's not say goodbye then.
不如就说
Let's just say.
以后见
See you later.
嘿
Hey.
别难过  儿子
It'll be okay, son.
嘿  走路能看着点儿吗
Hey, would you watch it?
没看见我们在这里呢吗  你个混蛋
I'm having a conversation here, you jerk!
老爸
Dad?
哇  这个城市的确可以改变你  咱们还是快离开吧
Wow, this city really does change you. Let's get out of here.
好了  查莉  老爸把PJ带回家了
Well, Charlie, dad brought P.J. back home.
现在他给老妈显摆在纽约照的照片
And now he's showing mom the pictures he took in New York.
这只是虫子和老鼠
It's just bugs and rats.
我知道  很棒吧
I know, right?
你去哪  我还有照片呢
Where are you going? I got more.
噢  说到照片  我今天拿到了学校的照片
Oh, speaking of photos, got my school picture back today
哇
Wow!
是啊  如果悲剧继续
Yeah, if the trend continues,
明年我将无牙外加光头
Next year I'll be toothless and bald.
好了  祝我好运吧  查莉
Well, wish me good luck, Charlie.
哇  难熬的一天
Wow, tough day.
你怎么样  挣到钱了吗
How you doing? You making any money?
你知道为什么吗  来了一位强敌啊
You know what problem is? New competition.
谢谢
Thank you.
走吧  老兄  换个地方
Come on, man, a better spot.
噢  歇歇吧
Oh, cut it out.
你又没困在箱子里
You are not in a box.